<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Development on EasyRPG Wiki</title><link>/development/</link><description>Recent content in Development on EasyRPG Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting started</title><link>/development/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development/getting-started/</guid><description>Understanding RPG Maker 2000 and 2003 To understand these systems, you need to know how it works first. To study them you need to learn about RPG Maker 2000/2003 first. RPG Maker 2000 and 2003 reached end of life in Japan and there are no trial versions available to download. Hovever, there are official English translations currently. There are no evaluation versions of them, but copies are usually cheap when in offer, from https://www.</description></item><item><title>RPG Maker test suite</title><link>/development/rpg-maker-test-suite/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development/rpg-maker-test-suite/</guid><description>For a better and faster emulation testing and bug detection, EasyRPG wants a test game containing all possible actions created with RPG Maker 2000 and 2003.
Project status In development.
&amp;lt;vgvgf&amp;gt; &amp;quot;stress&amp;quot; test should be added to the testsuite, including a map with lots of events &amp;lt;vgvgf&amp;gt; a map with lot of parallel events &amp;lt;vgvgf&amp;gt; a map with lots of events with moving routes &amp;lt;vgvgf&amp;gt; a map with lots of events with lots of pages, and else Maintainers Nobody currently.</description></item><item><title>Sample game</title><link>/development/sample-game/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development/sample-game/</guid><description>To demonstrate the capabilities of EasyRPG, a &amp;ldquo;sample game&amp;rdquo; created by users of the community is needed.
Project goals Create a full, playable (RPG) game. Make use of most or part of the features available. Use RTP material without complexes (of course, the game can use its own specific material). Requirements Use RPG Maker 2000 v1.51 or 1.52 in any language (more stable, 2003 can be used later using project import) while EasyRPG editor has not been completed yet.</description></item><item><title>Supported Encodings</title><link>/development/encoding-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development/encoding-list/</guid><description>This lists the currently supported encodings of liblcf.
Human readable name Mapping table (ICU) Codepage (iconv) Japanese ibm-943_P15A-2003 932 Korean windows-949-2000 949 ::: (needs ibm-1363_P11B-1998) Central Europe ibm-5346_P100-1998 1250 Cyrillic 1 ibm-5347_P100-1998 1251 Occidental 1 ibm-5348_P100-1997 1252 Greek 1 ibm-5349_P100-1998 1253 Hebrew 1 ibm-9447_P100-2002 1255 Arabic 1 2 ibm-9448_X100-2005 1256 Thai 1 windows-874-2000 874 Chinese simplified windows-936-2000 936 ::: (needs ibm-1386_P100-2001) Chinese traditional windows-950-2000 950 ::: (needs ibm-1373_P100-2002) Turkish ibm-5350_P100-1998 1254 Baltic ibm-9449_P100-2002 1257 with Euro&amp;#160;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description></item></channel></rss>