<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Player on EasyRPG Wiki</title><link>/user/player/</link><description>Recent content in Player on EasyRPG Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/user/player/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Button mapping</title><link>/user/player/buttons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user/player/buttons/</guid><description>The buttons are mapped similiar to the original RPG_RT but EasyRPG Player additionally provides more functions.
Normal Keys Buttons Function Up, K, Num8, W Move up Down, J, Num2, S Move down Left, H, Num4, A Move left Right, L, Num6, D Move right Enter, Z, Y, Space, Num Enter Actions (Select menu item and talk to NPCs) Esc, Backspace, X, C, V, B, N, Num0 Cancel (Open menu and cancel actions) Page down Scroll down one page in selection dialogs Page up Scroll up one page in selection dialogs Game specific keys These keys have game specific functions.</description></item><item><title>Command Line Arguments</title><link>/user/player/command-line/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user/player/command-line/</guid><description>This page could be outdated. Check https://easyrpg.org/player/manual/#_options for up to date command line documentation.
Argument Description --battle-test N Start a battle test with monster party N. --disable-audio Disable audio (in case you prefer your own music). --disable-rtp Disable support for the Run Time Package (RTP). --encoding N Instead of auto detecting the encoding or using the one in RPG_RT.</description></item><item><title>Game Compatibility List</title><link>/user/player/compat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user/player/compat/</guid><description>We are currently in the process to integrate wiki content into the main website. This forum topic serves as a way to add games to the official compatibility list in the meanwhile:
https://community.easyrpg.org/t/compatibility-list/283</description></item><item><title>Installation Guide</title><link>/user/player/install/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user/player/install/</guid><description>Get the latest build for your platform from our Jenkins Buildbot.
Extract the binary into the game folder and execute it. It behaves the same as RPG_RT with the exception, that RPG2k and RPG2k3 games are automatically detected, so one executable works for all games (as long as they are supported).
Most RPG Maker 2000/2003 games requires RTP. See rtp for installation instructions.</description></item><item><title>Runtime Package (RTP)</title><link>/user/player/rtp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user/player/rtp/</guid><description>Runtime Packages were intended to be a common asset library of graphics, music, and sounds that games often shared to save on disk space in the early days of computing (where floppy disks and dial-up modems were commonplace). A good way to understand the way it&amp;rsquo;s used is through Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s tools; developers that use Visual Studio often include Visual C++ Redistributables and the .NET Framework, or they have to tell the user to download it from Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s website.</description></item><item><title>Special Features</title><link>/user/player/special-features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user/player/special-features/</guid><description>This site lists all features that are different to the original RPG_RT.
Support for games of any language The original RPG_RT has problems handling games from countries that use characters which are not in the current codepage of the system.
Example: If you life in England your (Windows) system has the codepage for Western European (1252) set. With this codepage it&amp;rsquo;s not possible to play Russian or Japanese games because their characters are not encoded in this codepage.</description></item></channel></rss>