<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>RTP database on EasyRPG Wiki</title><link>/wiki/rtp-database/</link><description>Recent content in RTP database on EasyRPG Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/wiki/rtp-database/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2000 RTP</title><link>/wiki/rtp-database/2000-rtp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/wiki/rtp-database/2000-rtp/</guid><description>2000 RTP 465 files, 14 folders.
Translation table Note: this list is not up to date, the complete list is available at the source code:
https://github.com/EasyRPG/Player/blob/master/src/rtp_table.cpp#L20
If you know more translation languages or versions, both official or unofficial, please say where to get them to add to the table.
Backdrop Battle backgrounds. 25 PNG files. 320x160px.
Japanese (original) English (Don Miguel) English (official) ダンジョン1 Cave1 Dungeon1 ダンジョン2 LavaCave2 Dungeon2 ダンジョン3 IceCave3 Dungeon3 ダンジョン4 Cave4 Dungeon4 ダンジョン5 BrickCave5 Dungeon5 宇宙 Galaxy Space 山道 Canyon MountainPath 岩場 SnowCanyon RockyArea 廃墟 WasteRuins Ruins 森1 Forest1 Forest1 森2 Forest2 Forest2 橋 Bridge Bridge 毒沼 Swamp PoisonSwamp 海 Sea Sea 玉座 Castle Throne 異空間 LightSpeed StrangeSpace 砂浜 SeaBeach SandyBeach 砂漠 Desert Desert 神殿 Greece Shrine 空 Sky Sky 船上 Ship ShipDeck 草原 Grass Grassland 荒地 WasteLand Wasteland 街中 Town Downtown 雪原 Snow Snowfield Battle Battle animation effects.</description></item><item><title>2003 RTP</title><link>/wiki/rtp-database/2003-rtp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/wiki/rtp-database/2003-rtp/</guid><description>2003 RTP 675 files, 19 folders.
Translation table Note: this list is not up to date, the complete list is available at the source code:
https://github.com/EasyRPG/Player/blob/master/src/rtp_table.cpp#L20
If you know more translation languages or versions, both official or unofficial, please say where to get them to add to the table.
Vlad Kovnerov&amp;rsquo;s Russian RTP is supposed to be installed over Don Miguel’s RTP for RPG Maker 2000. Thus, most files would appear in two variants (2000 and 2003).</description></item><item><title>Migration (2000-2003)</title><link>/wiki/rtp-database/migration-2000-2003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/wiki/rtp-database/migration-2000-2003/</guid><description>Migration (2000-2003) Oficially, the migration between 2000 and 2003 projects is not 100% compatible. You can convert RPG Maker 2000 games into RPG Maker 2003 with the exception of the battles. Battle scenes are different.
EasyRPG wants to be compatible with both RPG Makers and make battle systems compatible and interchangeable. The monster graphic creation, to be the less work and time consuming possible, should be made with each sprite pose valid for both front and side battles using only one sprite.</description></item></channel></rss>