<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>RPG Maker technical details on EasyRPG Wiki</title><link>/development/technical-details/</link><description>Recent content in RPG Maker technical details on EasyRPG Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/development/technical-details/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Behavior of Common Events Called in RPG Maker 2003 Battle</title><link>/development/technical-details/common-events-battle-2003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development/technical-details/common-events-battle-2003/</guid><description>Behavior of Common Events Called in RPG Maker 2003 Battle Backup from https://web.archive.org/web/20080325201903/http://www.phylomortis.com/html/battlece.html
In RPG Maker 2003, common events can be called in battle. However, the behavior of some of the events is abnormal. The following table describes the effect of each event when called in battle. &amp;ldquo;Normal&amp;rdquo; means it has the effect you would expect. Otherwise, the actual effect will be described.
This list is current as of RPG Maker 2003 version 1.</description></item><item><title>Known patches</title><link>/development/technical-details/known-patches/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development/technical-details/known-patches/</guid><description>Known patches There are many different patches, hacks and other dubious methods to add new functionality to RPG Maker. This page tries to list them.
Unofficial RPG Maker functionality can come in the following forms:
modified engine executable, RPG_RT.exe, IPS file (they can be used to modify the executable by a tool like LunarIPS, or applied dynamically by DynRPG), HPA file to modify the executable by HyperPatcher2, manual replacement of values at given offsets (can be done in hex editor, or applied dynamically through QuickPatches in DynRPG) replacement for the audio library, Harmony.</description></item><item><title>RPG Maker 2003 version history</title><link>/development/technical-details/rpg-maker-2003-version-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development/technical-details/rpg-maker-2003-version-history/</guid><description>RPG Maker 2003 version history Backup from https://web.archive.org/web/20080325201422/http://www.phylomortis.com:80/html/rm2k3vh.html
This changelog does not include official English release patched version, only original Japanese updates.
Version 1.09 (January 14, 2004) Bug Fixes: When magic is reflected by a character with the &amp;ldquo;reflect&amp;rdquo; condition, the problem where the proper battle animation would sometimes not play on the new target was corrected. The problem where damage indication would occur on the fifth frame of the animation when using an item that mimics a skill was corrected.</description></item><item><title>RPG_RT.exe technical details</title><link>/development/technical-details/rpg_rt.exe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development/technical-details/rpg_rt.exe/</guid><description>RPG_RT.exe technical details This is implemented in Player now (except the behavior after renaming executable), remains here for reference only.
Specifying the command line RPG_RT.exe [TestPlay | BattleTest] [ShowTitle | HideTitle] [Fullscreen | Window] [n]
[TestPlay | BattleTest] There is a test mode of play. If the test is carried out of the game from the publisher, is sent TestPlay parameter. If the test is done battle since the publisher, is sent along with the parameter BattleTest the fourth parameter n.</description></item><item><title>System graphics technical details</title><link>/development/technical-details/system-graphics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development/technical-details/system-graphics/</guid><description>System graphics technical details This is implemented now in Player.
take_cheeze&amp;rsquo;s translation Basic Directory: &amp;ldquo;System/&amp;rdquo; Size: 160(width) x 80(height) Detail (x, y): coordinate (AxB): Size (Optionally &amp;ldquo;Pattern&amp;rdquo;) A: Window&amp;rsquo;s wallpaper (0,0) (32x32) Transparent Color: disabled If wallpaper type is TILE it will be tiled from left-top B: Window Parts (32, 0) (32x32) 0 - x: Frame y: Page Cursor Up z: Page Cursor Down / Waiting at text Transparent Color: enabled C: Command Cursor (64, 0) (32x32 x 2 Pattern) 0 - x: Frame y: Inside If wallpaper type is TILE it will be tiled from left-top Transparent Color: enabled D: Shop&amp;rsquo;s equip difference symbol (128, 0) (8x8 x 4 Pattern) 0: up 1: no difference 2: down 3: equipped Transparent Color: enabled E: Menu screen&amp;rsquo;s background (0, 32) (16x16) Transparent Color: disabled Only the left-top 1x1 pixel of this segment will be used F: Font&amp;rsquo;s shadow (16, 32) (16x16) Transparent Color, enabled Only the left-top 1x1 pixel of this segment will be used G: Timer character (32, 32) (8x16 x 12 character) (32, 32) 0 - 9 (112, 32) separator (120, 32) space Transparent Color: enabled H: Airship&amp;rsquo;s shadow (128, 32) (16x16 x 2 Pattern) Transparent Color: enabled &amp;lt;&amp;ndash; FIXME really semitransparent I: Font (0, 48) (16x16 x 10) 0 〜 9 (0, 64) (16x16 x 10) 10 〜 19 0 〜 19 Transparent Color: disabled &amp;lt;&amp;ndash; FIXME disagree, please verify Font Color Example * 0: Default * 0: Enable * 3: Disable * 1: Status * 2: Parameter Up * 3: Parameter Down * 1: Money * 4: HP Low * 4: MP Low Priority There is a priority of how it&amp;rsquo;s rendered.</description></item><item><title>What's new in RPG Maker 2003 that wasn't present in RPG Maker 2000</title><link>/development/technical-details/differences-rpg-maker-2000-2003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/development/technical-details/differences-rpg-maker-2000-2003/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s new in RPG Maker 2003 that wasn&amp;rsquo;t present in RPG Maker 2000 Backup from https://web.archive.org/web/20080323144634/http://www.phylomortis.com/html/rm2k3info.html
Items marked in bold and in parentheses are changes that have been made to the program through patches. You need the latest version of the program in order to utilize them.
Maximum level for heros is 99. Maximum HP is 9999. Maximum experience is 9999999. (Variables can now be up to seven digits, making the range -9999999 to 9999999.</description></item></channel></rss>