<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Uncategorized on EasyRPG Wiki</title><link>/uncategorized/</link><description>Recent content in Uncategorized on EasyRPG Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/uncategorized/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About EasyRPG</title><link>/uncategorized/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/uncategorized/about/</guid><description>EasyRPG is a project to create a free (as in freedom) Role Playing Game (RPG) creation tool.
The project consists on several tools and resources:
EasyRPG Editor EasyRPG Player RTP Replacement It is inspired on a commercial product called RPG Maker.
EasyRPG Editor The Editor is an application with a user interface to design roleplaying games.
It consists on:
A main map editor window where you can draw tile based maps A database window dialog where you can create or customize your characters, abilities, enemies, terrains, etc.</description></item><item><title>Frequently Asked Questions</title><link>/uncategorized/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/uncategorized/faq/</guid><description>Rights and selling Is there a catch to selling my game with EasyRPG? If you&amp;rsquo;re worried about having to share the source code because EasyRPG is open-source, you&amp;rsquo;ve been mistaken! Software that&amp;rsquo;s made with open-source compilers can be sold without having to share the source code. If that wasn&amp;rsquo;t the case, that would ruin a lot of businesses. Ren&amp;rsquo;Py is an example of an open-source engine that currently has games being sold on it.</description></item><item><title>Unzip games with specific encodings</title><link>/uncategorized/unzip-games/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/uncategorized/unzip-games/</guid><description>Some games are distributed in .zip packages. Lots of these have file names with non-ASCII encoding characters.
Most zip files are not using Unicode, so they need a special procedure to be unpacked properly.
Option 1: Unar unar (from The Unarchiver) automatically detects zip encoding and it&amp;rsquo;s available on most distributions. It also supports rar files.
Option 2: p7zip and encoding conversion Requirements:
Installed locales for languages to decode. p7zip-full convmv Commands for specific encodings:</description></item></channel></rss>