<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>RTP replacement on EasyRPG Wiki</title><link>/wiki/rtp-replacement/</link><description>Recent content in RTP replacement on EasyRPG Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/wiki/rtp-replacement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Media file format specifications</title><link>/wiki/rtp-replacement/media-file-format-specifications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/wiki/rtp-replacement/media-file-format-specifications/</guid><description>RPG Maker 2000 and 2003 supports the following file formats:
Graphic file formats Used in the following folders:
Backdrop Battle Battle2 (RPG Maker 2003 only) BattleCharSet (RPG Maker 2003 only) BattleWeapon (RPG Maker 2003 only) CharSet ChipSet FaceSet Frame GameOver Monster Panorama Picture System System2 (RPG Maker 2003 only) Title BMP BMP is a bitmap format used initially in Windows. There are different types but RPG Maker 2000 and 2003 only support BMP files with the following specifications:</description></item><item><title>RTP replacement contributions</title><link>/wiki/rtp-replacement/contributions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/wiki/rtp-replacement/contributions/</guid><description>Before contributing RTP replacement materials, we need to know some issues to prevent design problems:
The big table of characters RPG Maker 2000 and 2003 RTPs share lots of data between editions, but not only between them. Each character can be represented in multiple forms:
CharSet FaceSet BattleCharSet Monster The big table will be here. FIXME Assigned task: [fdelapena]
Monsters: One pose valid for both front and side battle If the pose of the Monster sprites is good it would be valid for both battle style scenes.</description></item><item><title>Setting the transparency correctly</title><link>/wiki/rtp-replacement/correct-transparency/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/wiki/rtp-replacement/correct-transparency/</guid><description>For compatibility with RPG Maker 2000/2003, EasyRPG uses a peculiar 8-bit format for PNGs. The first colour in the palette is considered transparent. So, if your graphics has a different colour arrangement, it might look transparent but won’t.
This is the recommended format to work with the RTP replacement material because people will be able to use your graphics in RPG Maker 2000/2003. Currently, the EasyRPG editor is not finished, so people still have rely to RPG Maker 2000/2003 for creating games to be played in EasyRPG.</description></item></channel></rss>